https://www.breitcantor.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyWe recognize that you may be concerned about
our use and disclosure of your personal information. Your privacy is
very important to us, and the following will inform you of the
information that we, Breit Cantor Grana Buckner, may collect from you,
and how it is used. By using our website, www.breitcantor.com, you are
accepting the practices described in this policy.Information CollectionWe
may collect non-personal information, such as a domain name and IP
Address. The domain name and IP address reveals nothing personal about
you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We
may also collect information about the type of Internet browser you are
using, operating system, what brought you to our Website, as well as
which of our Web pages you have accessed.Additionally, if you
communicate with us regarding our Website or our services, we will
collect any information that you provide to us in any such
communication.We may contact you via email in the future to tell
you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy
policy.Information UseWe use the collected information
primarily for our own internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining,
evaluating, and improving our services and Website, fulfilling requests
for information, and providing customer support.SecurityWe
follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the information
submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.If
we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that
information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can
verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web
browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the
web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information
transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only
employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for
example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally
identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store
personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.CookiesWe
use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a
site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and
identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a
cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more
than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also
enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the
experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any
personally identifiable information on our site.SharingWe
will not sell or otherwise provide the information we collect to
outside third parties for the purpose of direct or indirect mass email
marketing.We will disclose personal information and/or an IP
address, when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such
action is necessary to:Cooperate with the investigations of
purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or
comply with legal process served on our companyProtect and defend the rights or property of our Website and related propertiesIdentify
persons who may be violating the law, the rights of third parties, or
otherwise misusing our Website or its related propertiesPlease
keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal
information online – for example through e-mail, discussion boards, or
elsewhere – that information can be collected and used by others. In
short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the
public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in
return.Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the
secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible
whenever you are online.LinksThis Website may contain
links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for
the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our
users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy
statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable
information.Surveys & ContestsFrom time-to-time our
site may request information via surveys or contests. Participation in
these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose
whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information.
Information requested may include contact information (such as name and
shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age).
Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.
Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving
the use and satisfaction of this site.ConsentBy using
this Website, you consent to the collection and use of information as
specified above. If we make changes to our Privacy Policy, we will post
those changes on this page. Please review this page frequently to remain
up-to-date with the information we collect, how we use it, and under
what circumstances we disclose it. You must review the new Privacy
Policy carefully to make sure you understand our practices and
procedures.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at
(855) 212-8200
or via mail Attn: Privacy Officer, 7130 Glen Forest Drive, Suite 400, Richmond, VA 23226.We are personal injury attorneysFill out our contact form to speak to our experienced Virginia trial attorneys. Breit Cantor Grana Buckner has helped recover millions of dollars in medical malpractice cases. Learn how we can help you today.First Name*Last Name*Email*
Phone*Are you a new client?*Are you a new client?Yes, I am a potential new clientNo, I'm a current existing clientI'm neitherHow did you hear about us?*How did you hear about us?Attorney ReferralNon-Attorney ReferralGoogle or Bing SearchSocial MediaTelevisionRadioNot SureOtherMessagePhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged. Submit information
